With the knowledge gained from the previous module,
从上一个模块中获得的知识
we can now confidently move on to creating a basic
我们现在可以自信地继续创建一个基本的
T-shirt pattern.
T恤图案
At this point you will become acquainted with a portion
在这一点上，你将熟悉一部分
of the 2D tools and the sewing tools.
二维工具和缝纫工具
Now we will get another whole pallet of tools throughout
现在我们将得到另一整托盘的工具
the course as well,
课程也一样
but for now, let's focus on the basic ones for
但现在，让我们把重点放在基本问题上
creating patterns.
正在创建模式
Tools for making patterns are the Polygon tool rectangle tool,
制作图案的工具是多边形工具矩形工具
and circle tool which we use depending on the shape
以及我们根据形状使用的圆形工具
that we want.
我们想要的
So for now, let's grab the rectangle tool and you'll
所以现在，让我们抓住矩形工具，你会
see that I'm able to create a rectangle in the
我可以在中创建一个矩形
2D window by simply just clicking on it,
只需点击二维窗口
and I get this dialog box where I can manually
我得到了一个可以手动操作的对话框
input the width and the height,
输入宽度和高度
or I can just go and drag to create a
或者我可以直接拖动来创建
rectangle.
矩形
So let's just create the simple rectangle over
让我们在上面创建一个简单的矩形
the silhouette. Now, since we're creating a shirt,
剪影。既然我们要做一件衬衫
we're starting off by creating only the left part,
我们从只创建左边开始
which is actually the right part in the 3D window,
它实际上是三维窗口中的正确部分
and we could make a shirt out of one pattern
我们可以用一种图案做一件衬衫
in the front,
在前面